[{
    "tag":"Java",
    "NoOfQuestion":1741335,
    "Questions": [
        {
            "question":"Why is processing a sorted array faster than processing an unsorted array?",
            "votes":25137,
            "NoOfAnswer":26,
            "views":"1.6M"
        },
        {
            "question":"Why is subtracting these two times (in 1927) giving a strange result?",
            "votes":7051,
            "NoOfAnswer":11,
            "views":"714k"
        },
        {
            "question":"Is Java “pass-by-reference” or “pass-by-value”?",
            "votes":6842,
            "NoOfAnswer":83,
            "views":"2.1M"
        }
    ]
},
{
    "tag":"python",
    "NoOfQuestion":1612220,
    "Questions": [
        {
            "question":"What does the “yield” keyword do?",
            "votes":10772,
            "NoOfAnswer":42,
            "views":"2.4M"
        },
        {
            "question":"What does if __name__ == “__main__”: do?",
            "votes":6507,
            "NoOfAnswer":34,
            "views":"3.3M"
        },
        {
            "question":"Does Python have a ternary conditional operator?",
            "votes":6398,
            "NoOfAnswer":28,
            "views":"2.0M"
        }
    ]
},
{
    "tag":"Javascript",
    "NoOfQuestion":2140949 ,
    "Questions": [
        {
            "question":"How can I remove a specific item from an array?",
            "votes":8924,
            "NoOfAnswer":101,
            "views":"7.5M"
        },
        {
            "question":"How do I check if an element is hidden in jQuery?",
            "votes":7972,
            "NoOfAnswer":59,
            "views":"2.8M"
        },
        {
            "question":"What does “use strict” do in JavaScript, and what is the reasoning behind it?",
            "votes":7727,
            "NoOfAnswer":28,
            "views":"1.1M"
        }
    ]
},
{
    "tag":"HTML",
    "NoOfQuestion":1045064,
    "Questions": [
        {
            "question":"Why does HTML think “chucknorris” is a color?",
            "votes":7876,
            "NoOfAnswer":9,
            "views":"619K"
        },
        {
            "question":"How do I check whether a checkbox is checked in jQuery?",
            "votes":4724,
            "NoOfAnswer":66,
            "views":"4.3M"
        },
        {
            "question":"How to horizontally center a <div>",
            "votes":4505,
            "NoOfAnswer":113,
            "views":"4.2M"
        }
    ]
},
{
    "tag":"Jquery",
    "NoOfQuestion":1007257,
    "Questions": [
        {
            "question":"How do I check if an element is hidden in jQuery?",
            "votes":7972,
            "NoOfAnswer":59,
            "views":"2.8M"
        },
        {
            "question":"How do I redirect to another webpage?",
            "votes":7717,
            "NoOfAnswer":58,
            "views":"6.5M"
        },
        {
            "question":"How do I return the response from an asynchronous call?",
            "votes":5778,
            "NoOfAnswer":42,
            "views":"1.6M"
        }
    ]
},
{
    "tag":"c#",
    "NoOfQuestion":1454436,
    "Questions": [
        {
            "question":"What is the difference between String and string in C#?",
            "votes":6769,
            "NoOfAnswer":62,
            "views":"1.1M"
        },
        {
            "question":"How to enumerate an enum",
            "votes":3906,
            "NoOfAnswer":30,
            "views":"816k"
        },
        {
            "question":"How can I cast int to enum?",
            "votes":3341,
            "NoOfAnswer":31,
            "views":"1.5M"
        }
    ]
}]